livestation.com 2011-11-01

# Livestation privacy policy | Livestation

We respect your right to privacy and it is our policy to comply with all applicable privacy and data protection laws. We are committed to protecting your personal information when using our software or services. 

Livestation is a software product and service provided by Livestation Limited, a UK Registered Company. In this document "Livestation", "our", "us" or "we" all refer to Livestation Limited. 

This privacy policy (the "Policy") describes how we protect your privacy when we collect personal information through your use of the Livestation application (the "Software") or the www.livestation.com web service (the "Website"). In this Policy, the term "Personal Information" means information that identifies you personally, alone or in combination with other information available to us. We also collect information that does not identify you personally. 

  1. ## Your consent

When registering to use our Software or by using the Website or providing Personal Information to us, you are consenting to the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Information as described in this Policy. 

If you do not consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Policy, please do not use the Software or Website. 

If you are less than 18 years of age you must get the permission of your parent or guardian before you provide any personal information to us. 

If your child has submitted personal information and you would like to request that such information be deleted from our records, you may do so by contacting us at the address at the end of this Policy. 

  2. ## Limitations

To the extent required by applicable law, whenever Livestation collects Personal Information via the Livestation Software or on the Website, we will: 

    * Provide timely and appropriate notice to you about the use of your Personal Information;
    * Collect, use, disclose and transfer your Personal Information as described in this Policy only with your consent, which may be expressed or implied, depending on the sensitivity of the personal information, legal requirements, and other factors;
    * Collect your relevant, adequate and not excessive Personal Information only for specific, limited purposes;
    * Process your Personal Information in a manner consistent with the purposes for which it was originally collected or to which you have subsequently consented;
    * Take commercially reasonable steps to ensure that your Personal Information is reliable for its intended use, accurate, complete, and, where necessary, kept up-to-date;
    * Not use your Personal Information for direct marketing purposes without giving you an opportunity to "opt-out"; and
    * Take appropriate measures, by contract or otherwise, to provide adequate protection for personal information that is disclosed to a third party or transferred to another country, including internal transfers or to our associated companies.
  3. ## Use of Personal Information

We only collect Personal Information that we believe will improve our service to you. We may use this information to improve the service, analyse technical issues, learn about our audience, suggest programming, or deliver advertisements. 

We may collect the information you knowingly and voluntarily provide when you use the Livestation Software or Website. This may include Personal Information that you provide when you sign up, when you complete a survey, or when you ask us a question or email us with feedback. 

This Personal Information may include: 

    * Personal Details - We may ask you for information such as your age, your gender, country, and your interests. 
    * Viewing History - We may also collect information on channels, programmes, advertisements, emails or web pages viewed.

We may use the information we collect for other business purposes such as providing customer service, fraud prevention, market research, improving our products and services, and providing you or your company with information and offers we believe may be of interest to you. We may also remove all the personally identifiable information and use the remaining data for historical, statistical or scientific purposes. 

  4. ## Collecting Personal Information

When you use the Livestation Software or Website we may collect information that is sent to us automatically by the Livestation software or your web browser. 

This information may include or incorporate your IP internet address, your MAC network address, the name and version of your operating system and the name and version of your browser, together with other information used to configure our software for your computer. 

This information does not identify you personally, but the registration process for the Livestation software does. 

We may use this information to determine from which country you are accessing the services and to determine which channels are available to you. 

We may also pass on your login information to a channel provider or platform operator in the case of subscription channels or premium programming to enable you to view such channels or programmes. 

We may also store and transfer a small file known as a 'cookie' to save and maintain information and preferences while you are using the Livestation software or Website and between sessions. 

We may also save other information on the storage system of your computer to enable the Livestation Software or Website to store preferences. 

The Livestation Software may also be used to send us a log file when there is a problem. This log file contains information about your use of our software and technical information about your computer to enable us to diagnose problems. 

  5. ## Sharing Personal Information

Livestation may share your personal information with third parties we use to perform certain services for us such as support or technical functions. We will limit the information we share and these third parties are required to use the personal information we share with them only to perform services on our behalf and to treat your personal information as strictly confidential. 

Livestation may also share your personal information with other Livestation businesses or with third parties who partner with us to provide products and services to our customers. In this case we will require such business units or business partners to use the personal information we share with them in a manner consistent with the purposes for which it was originally collected or to which you subsequently consented and only as permitted under this Policy and all applicable privacy and data protection laws. 

In certain limited circumstances we may share or transfer personal information to unrelated third parties. This may be at your request, to comply with a legal requirement or court order, to investigate a possible crime, or a matter on which we require legal advice or under similar circumstances. In such cases we will take appropriate steps to protect your personal information. 

  6. ## Security of Personal Information

Livestation will maintain reasonable safeguards to protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of your personal information. For example, we use encryption to protect any passwords and we restrict access to information both physically and logically. Although we use security measures to help protect your personal information against unauthorised disclosure, misuse or alteration, as is the case with all public computer networks, we cannot guarantee the security of information provided over the Internet and will not be responsible for breaches of security beyond our reasonable control. 

  7. ## Links to third-party services

The Livestation Software and our Website may contain references or links to third-party services that are not operated by Livestation. These references or links are provided as a service and do not imply any endorsement of the activities or content of such services or any association with their operators. Livestation does not control such services and is not responsible for their content, security or privacy practices. You therefore access such services at your own risk. You should review the privacy policy or terms and conditions of use associated with such services before using them or providing personal or other information. 

  8. ## Retention and deletion of Personal Information

We will retain the Personal Information we collect only as long as necessary to provide the services, products and information you request or as permitted by applicable law. We also periodically destroy information in accordance with our company policies. 

We aim to respond to any request for deletion of personal information within seven days. Please note that this may prevent you from using our software. Requests should be sent to the contact address listed at the end of this Policy. 

  9. ## Access to Personal Information

You may review, correct and update the personal information that you provide to us by using the feedback mechanisms provided by the Website or by using the contact details listed at the end of this Policy. 

  10. ## Financial Information

All payments on the Livestation website are managed by Paypal.

Livestation does not store any of your financial information. Livestation merely stores an identification token which is used to link your account to the Paypal gateway.

  11. ## Contacting you

Livestation may contact you: 

    * In relation to the functioning of our software or to ensure that we can deliver services to you;
    * To invite you to participate in voluntary surveys about Livestation services;
    * In relation to any contribution you have made to a Livestation user survey or message board;
    * For marketing purposes where you have specifically agreed to this; or
    * Where you have opted to receive further correspondence.
  12. ## Changes to this Policy

We will always post the latest Policy on the Website. 

We may introduce new features or services from time to time as we develop the service. In order to be able to do this we need to be able to change our privacy policies. 

Livestation reserves the right to update or modify this Policy, at any time and without prior notice, by posting the revised version of this Policy on the Website. Your continued use of the Website after any such changes to the Policy constitutes your acceptance of those changes. 

Except for amendments required by law, the Policy at the date that the personal information is collected shall apply to your previously provided Personal Information and any new Personal Information you provide to us. 

  13. ## Contact details

If you have any questions about this Policy or our use of your Personal Information, you may contact us either by email to [privacy@livestation.com](mailto:privacy@livestation.com) or by writing to us at: Livestation Privacy Officer, Livestation Ltd, The Trampery, 13-19 Bevenden Street, London, N1 6AA, United Kingdom.
